George S. Schuyler Papers
George S. Schuyler Papers
- Writings
  - Typescripts, periodical
    - North American Newspaper Alliance (NANA), 1965-1968 (Box 23)
      Feb 18, 1968 Negro Business Fears "Hot Summer"
      Feb 26, 1968 Commission Produces Expected Whitewash
      Apr 5, 1968 Dr. King: Non-violence Always Ends Violently
      May 11, 1968 America Moving Toward Apartheid
      Jun 13, 1968 Washington Awaits Juneteenth Day
    - The Priest, 1967 (Box 23)
      The Limits of Integration Jan 24, 1967
    - Review of the News, 1967 (Box 23)
      May 30, 1967 The Perils of Provocation
      Jun 26, 1967 Burying Our Oldest Bugaboo
      Jul 24, 1967 Rumplestiltskins Unlimited
      Aug 31, 1967 Black Power Apartheid
      Oct 6, 1967 Love's Labor Lost in Mississippi
      Oct 31, 1967 School for Treason
      Dec 4, 1967 Socialism's Failure in Education
    - Review of the News, 1968 (Box 23)
      Jan 1, 1968 The Many Faces of Open Housing
      Feb 3, 1968 A Closet Full of Skeletons
      Feb 28, 1968 The Desperados
      Apr 5, 1968 Tempests in the Coffee-pot
      May 4, 1968 Toward a Long, Cool Summer
      Jun 5, 1968 Collective Guilt
      Jul 2, 1968 The Great Ghetto Swindle
      Aug 1, 1968 A Massacre of Fictions
      Sep 4, 1968 Chicago: Ominous Portent
      Oct 3, 1968 Narcotics, Anyone?
      Oct 31, 1968 The Drive for Discrimination
      Dec 1, 1968 NAACP: A Great Light Dawns
    - Review of the News, 1969 (Box 23)
      Jan 6, 1969 How Black is Your Alma Mater?
      Feb 5, 1969 Who's Loony Now?
      Mar 3, 1969 Orphans of the Storm
      Jun 27, 1969 Cinema Sodom
      Jul 3, 1969 No Hidin' Place
      Aug 7, 1969 Dangerous Games
      Sep 2, 1969 Why Not Detention?
      Oct 6, 1969 More Nerve Than Tracy!
      Nov 5, 1969 The "Black Capitalism" Hoax
      Nov 7, 1969 Canonization of Dr. King
      Dec 6, 1969 The Foresight Saga
    - Review of the News, 1970 (Box 23)
      Jan 3, 1970 Insanity Fair
      Feb 3, 1970 Friends of Foes
      Mar 5, 1970 Mortarboard Madness
      May 28, 1970 Reincarnation of the Jungle
      Jun 14, 1970 Vouchers for Freedom
      Aug 3, 1970 The General Opts Out
      Nov 7, 1970 New Dope for Old
      Dec 28, 1970 Educational Phantasmagoria
      Mar 5, 1971 Mau-Mauing Marches On
      Jun 1, 1971 Miseducation
      Jun 5, 1971 In Defense of Snooping
    - Miscellaneous, 1967; undated (Box 23)
      Review: The Perpetual Negro Conundrum: Negro Social and Political Thought by Howard Brotz and Freedom-When? by James Farmer, 1967
      Report on Levee Work Along the Mississippi River in Louisiana and Mississippi, undated
  - Typescripts, speeches
    - Itinerary Logs, 1965-1968 (Box 23)
    - Speeches, 1951-1967 (Box 23)
      Was There Much Ado About Nothing? Josephine Baker vs. Stork Club circa 1951
      [80th birthday of Carl Van Vechten] Jun 20, 1960
      The Case Against the Civil Rights Bill Nov 11, 1963
      [Introduction] Apr 19, 1965
      The United Nations Apr 26, 1965 - two versions
      Domestic Peace Corps. Aug 30, 1965
      Black Men as Fighters Spring 1966
      The Siege of Mississippi Jun 29, 1966
      The Future of the American Negro Apr 6, 1967
      [Acceptance Speech, Portchester, New York, American Legion Club Jun 16, 1967
    - Speeches, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
      Rhodesian Realities Jan 5, 1968 - 2 copies
      The Need for Conservatisim Feb 15, 1968
      Build With Youth for a Better World Apr 20, 1968
      Civil Rights May 5, 1968 - 2 copies
      America's and South Africa's Multiracialism Jul 5, 1968
      Conservative Priority List Nov 16, 1968
      The Communist Conspiracy Against Negroes Feb 18, 1969
      The Inner Rot of Society Nov 8, 1969
      Youth in the Mire Nov 20, 1969